<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Document and Payment on Nervatura</title>
    <link>/nervatura/docs/client/document/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Document and Payment on Nervatura</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/nervatura/docs/client/document/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Document</title>
      <link>/nervatura/docs/client/document/document/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/nervatura/docs/client/document/document/</guid>
      <description>Overview # Nervatura was made for being able to store all data generated during ones working process. OFFER type forms are used to record the given (CUSTOMER) and also the received (SUPPLIER) offers/quotations. If any of the offers finally results in business deal, then its data are easy to use for further transaction types.&#xA;The ORDER, WORKSHEET and RENTAL transaction types play a significant role in the workflow. They gather all those goods/services that we either committed to deliver or we expect to be delivered by our suppliers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Item</title>
      <link>/nervatura/docs/client/document/item/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/nervatura/docs/client/document/item/</guid>
      <description>Input fields # Product No. # One of the items of the PRODUCT. Field filling is compulsory. Its value can be defined using a search field but can be set with the help of a barcode as well.&#xA;When the product has been chosen the program will display on the form all available (already defined) data about the product: Description, Unit, Tax Rate, Discount, Unit Price.&#xA;The price of the product is searched by taking into account the following criteria: (product and transaction side), current day, currency, volume, customer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payment</title>
      <link>/nervatura/docs/client/document/payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/nervatura/docs/client/document/payment/</guid>
      <description>Input fields # Document No. # Unique ID, generated at the first data save. The format and value of the next data in row is taken from the DOCUMENT NUMBERING (code = bank_transfer/cash) data series.&#xA;Reference No. # Other reference or bank statement number. Optional, its value can be freely defined.&#xA;Creation # Date of creation. Automatic value, cannot be changed.&#xA;Closed # Technical closing of the document.&#xA;If set, document data become read only.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
